<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aubrey Taylor | Los Angeles based web / software developer.</title>
    <description>Aubrey Taylor is an LA based web / software developer specializing in rich, interactive HTML, JS, CSS based web experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://aubz.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://aubz.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:24:42 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 10:24:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Plus K, Forever?</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;omg&quot;&gt;OMG!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With only two weeks left, I’m a bit behind with this announcement. What’s new. Ha ha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-sound-of-a-distant-question-popping&quot;&gt;The Sound of a Distant Question Popping…&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may know, Kelly and I have been together for over three years. Together through the good and the bad, the ecstatic and the frustrating, the worrisome and celebratory time we’ve both grown a lot. The beautiful part is that our Journey together has been a true partnership and we’re both better people for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The relationship Kelly and I share is a rare gift. And it’s for that reason, among many, that I’ve decided to ask her to marry me! Yay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-a-clever-ruse&quot;&gt;First, A Clever Ruse&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ok, maybe not so clever (ha ha)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly loves camping. I’ve never (really) been. While pining over how to set this up, preferably somewhere memorable and not cheesy, it came to me—What if I asked her to go camping? We could share a fun adventure that would come to a (hopefully) brilliant end!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, for my birthday, Kelly and I took a miniature road trip up Pacific Highway 1 to Big Sur and Carmel. To date, one of the most beautiful wildernesses I’ve seen. I mean, the ocean plus the woods?! Crazy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way home we stopped at a wonderful little spot called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hikinginbigsur.com/hikes_sanddollar.html&quot;&gt;Sand Dollar Beach&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sand-dollar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was one of our favorite spot on the trip. The water is so clear and blue. It was off-season and no one was around. We (and the pups) had the whole beach to ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought to myself: “Myself, this is the perfect spot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily there’s a couple campgrounds nearby, and we’ve already made reservations at &lt;a href=&quot;http://campone.com/campsites/plaskett-creek/&quot;&gt;Plaskett Creek&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plaskett.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-heres-the-plan&quot;&gt;So here’s the plan:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Ask Kelly to go camping!&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Reserve camping site!&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Get camping gear!&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have a day of romantic and fun hiking / camping.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;End up at Sand Dollar beach near the end of the day.(around sunset)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove ring secretly packed into backpack.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ask my wonderful lady if she’ll go steady—permanently!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;now-to-the-shiny-bauble&quot;&gt;Now to the Shiny Bauble&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a preview of the ring:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/bauble.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly and I “shopped” (meaning I slyly sent her web links to “checkout” to get her “opinion” on some ambiguous future engagement) for this ring at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brilliantearth.com/&quot;&gt;Brilliant Earth&lt;/a&gt;; a wonderful, on-line ring store that employs &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brilliantearth.com/why-buy-from-brilliant-earth/&quot;&gt;earth and humanity friendly practices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture is from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brilliantearth.com/&quot;&gt;Brilliant Earth&lt;/a&gt; site, but it’s almost identical to the one I received. Sadly, it does it no justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real pictures coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had the ring since November or so. Currently the ring is sitting, hidden, in a guitar case, just feet from where Kelly sleeps. Ha ha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some morose part of me chuckles at this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wish-me-luck&quot;&gt;Wish Me Luck!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s all going down between &lt;strong&gt;February 14&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (oh dang! right on Valentine’s Day Weekend!? Such a stud!) &lt;strong&gt;and 17&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and, so far, the plan has come together nicely. I’m currently planning on that Sunday, around sunset, to drop a knee and say mushy heartfelt things all while holding a shiny, sunset-reflecting bauble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wish me luck!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://aubz.me/hidden/2015/02/02/a-plus-k/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://aubz.me/hidden/2015/02/02/a-plus-k/</guid>
        
        
        <category>hidden</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aubz.me Launches</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It feels good scratching an item off the ol’ To-Do List I’ve been neglecting for far too long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After work and personal projects, maintaining – let alone creating – a personal site ranks pretty low on the scale of &lt;em&gt;“Things I Like to do With My Free Time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, my past attempts have floundered after running into complex installation / hosting requirements, complicated interfaces, my distaste for Rich Text Editors, subscription fees, and sometimes my own laziness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, an impromptu chat with a &lt;a href=&quot;http://nkantar.com&quot;&gt;friend&lt;/a&gt; lead me to &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;; a really handy “blog-aware”, static-site generator that eschews complex CMS and database for &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; and static pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I can create posts in my beloved Markdown, have complete control over my site, and never have to touch a CMS interface. Woot!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here’s to Jekyll, this blog, and writing more. &lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-beer&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Initial development involved approximately one &lt;em&gt;casual&lt;/em&gt; week to stand up and befriend Jekyll, create a custom design, and write this post. Not bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Links --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 11:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://aubz.me/projects/2015/01/04/aubz-me-launches/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://aubz.me/projects/2015/01/04/aubz-me-launches/</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
