<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aubrey Taylor | Los Angeles based web / software developer.</title>
    <description>Aubrey Taylor is an LA based web / software developer specializing in rich, interactive HTML, JS, CSS based web experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://aubz.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://aubz.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 22:48:12 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 22:48:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aubz.me Launches</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It feels good scratching an item off the ol’ To-Do List I’ve been neglecting for far too long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After work and personal projects, maintaining – let alone creating – a personal site ranks pretty low on the scale of &lt;em&gt;“Things I Like to do With My Free Time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, my past attempts have floundered after running into complex installation / hosting requirements, complicated interfaces, my distaste for Rich Text Editors, subscription fees, and sometimes my own laziness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, an impromptu chat with a &lt;a href=&quot;http://nkantar.com&quot;&gt;friend&lt;/a&gt; lead me to &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;; a really handy “blog-aware”, static-site generator that eschews complex CMS and database for &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; and static pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I can create posts in my beloved Markdown, have complete control over my site, and never have to touch a CMS interface. Woot!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Look out for a post about my experience implementing Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here’s to Jekyll, this blog, and writing more. &lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-beer&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Initial development involved approximately one &lt;em&gt;casual&lt;/em&gt; week to stand up and befriend Jekyll, create a custom design, and write this post. Not bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Links --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 11:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://aubz.me/projects/2015/01/04/aubz-me-launches.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://aubz.me/projects/2015/01/04/aubz-me-launches.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
